<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>atDude Tutorial on</title><link>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/</link><description>Recent content in atDude Tutorial on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>App Architecture</title><link>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/3-app_architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/3-app_architecture/</guid><description>In this tutorial, we will we&amp;rsquo;ll implement the MVC+S architecture pattern in our app.
We will create the folders that will store our models, views, commands and services.
Models #
The models are only concerned with storing and manipulation of data our app needs.
In your terminal type:
mkdir lib/models The model files will be saved in this folder.
Views #
The views are the widgets and screen in our application.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/2-getting_started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/2-getting_started/</guid><description>In this tutorial, we will be using VS Code, but feel free to use any editor of your choice.
To get started, open your terminal and cd to the folder where you want to start this project. Type the following in your terminal:
dart pub global activate at_app The above command will allow you to run the at_app scripts from the command line when you are not currently inside a package.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/1-introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.atsign.com/tutorials/at-dude/1-introduction/</guid><description>In this tutorial we will build the atDude app. This app is a secure, end-to-end encrypted, peer-to-peer application that allows you to send &amp;lsquo;dudes&amp;rsquo; to your contacts!
The longer you press and hold the Dude button, the longer your sent dude will be! You can keep up-to-date with your &amp;lsquo;dude&amp;rsquo; stats to see how much duding you&amp;rsquo;ve done!
This app is built on the atPlatform. The atPlatform is an open-source backend platform that allows developers to build end-to-end encrypted applications.</description></item></channel></rss>